Guide to the Norfolk County, Collection of English Deeds ca. 1409-ca.1826
University of Chicago Library
Norfolk County, Collection of English Deeds
ca. 1409-ca.1826
4 linear feet (8 boxes)
Special Collections Research Center, University of Chicago Library 1100 East 57th Street Chicago, Illinois 60637 U.S.A.
Primarily property deeds. Also contains some wills and related documents.
Information on Use
Access
No restrictions.
Scope Note
English deeds, wills and related documents from Norfolk, fifteenth to nineteenth- centuries.
Related Resources
The following related resources are located in the Department of Special Collections:
http://www.lib.uchicago.edu/e/spcl/select.html
Subject Headings
Norfolk (England); Norfolk (England) -- History -- Sources.; Deeds.; Legal documents.; Manuscripts.; Manuscripts, English.; Wills.
INVENTORY
- Deed, 25 July 11 Henry IV (1409) Grantor, Johes Smyth of Wytton Grantee, Robto Thurkyld of Posswyke; Thome Sigard of Posswyke Parcels, 3 pieces of land in Wytton Witnesses, John Spayne, Rica Atteyate; Rico Chapman, Eda Eleynie; Willo Jakys (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Deed, 31 August 8 Edward IV (1468) Grantor, Agnes Spayne (former wife of John Spayne of Possewyk) Grantee, John Spayne (son of Robt. Spayne); Thome Kyssex; Thome Holar; John Fuller. Land in Possewyk (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Deed, 17 July 16 Edward IV 1. William Noloth 2. [?] Lands in Hebyngham (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Deed, 10 October 17 Edward IV 1. John Aubry; John Cook (draper); Robert Ayliner (alderman of Norwich); Hugo Cotes; John Bisshop; and William Kyng 2. Robert Osberne (of Norwich); John Gosselyn; Robto Longe (dyer); and John Attemere Land in Possewyk (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Deed, 4 November 17 Edward IV 1. Anna Boleyn 2. John Spany of Possewyk Manor of Possewyk (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Deed, Jan. 17 Edward IV 1. Robert Brampton; Johes Heydon; John Fyncham 1. John Brampton (son of Robt. Brampton); Johanne (former wife of John Bokkyng) Manors of Walshams and Bryans in Northwalsham (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Deed, Feb. 3 Henry VI Grantor, ? of Possewyk Grantee, ? Land in Possewyk, etc. (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Deed, 10 November 16 Henry VI Land in Possewyk (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Deed, 31 May 29 Henry VI Grantor: Johes Halman (alias Alman) Grantee: Willmo Rokewode; Jon Astelee; Edmundo Wichyngham; Nicho Westhalle; and Robto Alman Land in Thynyng, Wooddallyng, Heydon (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Deed, 17 October 33 Henry VI (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Deed, 10 December 35 Henry VI 1. William Spany of Norwich; John Yates of Norwich; John Wkyiesan of Possewyk 2. Robert Spany of Possewyk; John Leukenore of Reedham; John Germeye of Reedham; Thome Holler of Reedham; John Fuller Lands in Possewyk (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Deed (Grant), 31 December 7 Henry VIII 1. Johes 2. Johe Payne of Yaxham; Thomas Payne; William ----- Lands in Yaxham (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Deed, 9 March 19 Henry VIII Manor of Dylham (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 2 deeds, 2 November 37 Henry VIII 1. Robtus Chappman of Magna Plumsted 2. John Bulleman of Magna Plumsted Land in Magna Plumsted 6 October 1 Edward VI 1. Robert Chapman of Magna Plumsted 2. William Nuttell of Norwich Land in Magna Plumsted (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Indenture of Exchange, 20 November 1 Edward VI 1. Sir William Fermor, knight 2. Robert Dume Manor of Newton; manor of Pynkeney, Vegvylle and Lucys (?) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Deed, 3 March 4-5 Philip and Mary 1. John Wynter of Carbroke (Carbrook) 2. Thomas and John Gawdron Land in Carbroke (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Deed (Lease for 200 years), 10 June 15 Elizabeth 1. Nicholas and Cecyly Gylmyn of Norwich 2. Ralph Gylmyn of Norwich Land in Shipm and Carbrocke (Carbrook) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Deed, 2 July 19 Elizabeth 1. Nicholas Stanton of Stratton St. Marie 2. Thomas Towneshend of Stratton St. Marie Land in Stratton (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Deed, 3 May 40 Elizabeth 1. Sir Robert Ratcliff, Earl of Suffolk 2. Thomas Kempe of Little Bricett in Suffofk and Thomas Kirbye of Honham in Essex Manor of Burwelles in East Ruston (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Deed, 11 August 1607 5 James I 1. Alice Paston of Oxmeade, Norfolk (widow of Richard Lambert, alderman of London); Edmonde Lambert of Boyton in Wiltes 2. Elias Holman of London Lands in Levesham, Kent (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Deed, 27 March 7 James I 1. Peter Gray of Wooddallinge 2. Richard Jarvis of Wooddallinge Land in Wooddallinge (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Deed, 2 June 11 James I (1613) 1. Maria Gray of Wooddallinge 2. John Clarkson Land in Wooddallinge (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Deed, 16 February 14 James I (1616) 1. Rogerus Greene of Dunham, Norfolk 2. Richard Alpe of Dunham Lands in Dunham (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Deed, 12 April 14 James I 1. John Blomefield of Roydon, Norfolk 2. John Horner of Roydon Lands in Roydon (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Deed, 26 February 17 James I (1619) 1. Franciscus Wattes of Matteshall, Norfolk 2. Stepho Gooche of Carleton, George Aldred of Barforth Lands in Matteshall (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Deed, 31 May 17 James I 1. Robt. Halman of Swaffham Market 2. Thomas Theodericke of Swaffham Market One messuage called the Old Swann in Swaffham Market (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Deed, 2 October 1 Charles (1625) 1. William Howlett of S. Burlingham 2. Robert Mellinge of Somleyton, Suffolk Land in South Burlingham, Norfolk (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Deed (Release), 21 November 1 Charles I (1625) 1. William Coppinge of London (heir of Thomas Coppinge of Woodeton, Norfolk 2. Thomas Carsey of Woodeton, Norfolk Land in Woodeton (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Deed, 16 November 2 Charles I (1626) 1. Anthony Starlinge of Colbye, Norfolk 2. Thomas Marsham of Stratton Streles Land in Colbye (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Deed, 8 October 4 Charles I (1628) 1. William Gelsthorpe of IIford, Essex 2. Henry Postell of Happisburghe, Norfolk Land in Happisburghe (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Deed, 29 October 4 Charles I (1628) 1. John Havers of Shelfanger 2. Andrew Wills, thelder of Royden; Andrewe Wills, the Younger of Roydon The Gravel Pit in Roydon (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Deed, 5 October 5 Charles I (1629) 1. William Clarke of Trymyngham, Norfolk 2. Robert and Alice Andrews of Trymyngham Land in Trymyngham (3 rods) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Deed, 16 November 5 James I (1629) 1. Robert Tailer of Corpestie, Norfolk 2. William Skottowe of Wooddallinge; Thomas Norton of Heidon Lands in Burston, Norfolk (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Deed, 26 March 5 Charles I (1630) 1. Elizabeth Page of Hyngham, Norfolk; Thomas Page (son of Elizabeth); Martin Alden of Hyngham, Norfolk 2. Anne Sample of Hyngham Land in Hyngham, Norfolk (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Deed, 5 October 6 Charles I (1630) 1. Anthony Starlinge of Colbye, Norfolk 2. Richard Harman of Norwich Land in Colbye, Norfolk (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Deed, 9 August 7 Charles I (1631) 1. Phillip Greene of Dunham 2. Thomas Haylett of Southacre Land in Dunham (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Deed (Lease), 24 December 8 Charles I (1632) 1. Sir Thomas Southwell of Wood Rising 2. William Welles of Carbrook Land in Carbrook (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Deed, 15 June 11 Charles I (1635) 1. Thomas Nurse of Westderham, Norfolk 2. William Cooper of Hilborowe, Norfolk 18 acres land in Hilborowe (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Deed, 10 October 11 Charles I (1635) 1. William George of Rockland St. Peters; Mary Litmer of Carbrooke 2. Michem Hardy of Carbrooke Land in Carbrooke (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Deed, 13 March 12 Charles I (1636) 1. Richard Norton of South Creike, Norfolk 2. Thomas Fyndall of South Creike, Norfolk Land in South Creike (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Deed, 12 December 13 Charles I (1637) 1. Thomas Lincolne, Mayor of Thetford 2. Daniel Smith of Watton, Norfolk Land in Carbrook (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Deed (Lease for 1,000 years), 11 December 16 Charles I (1640) 1. John Kettle of Pulham St. Mary Magdale 2. Alice Smith and William Smith (her son) of South Burlingham 5 acres in South Birlingham (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Deed, 15 June 1641 1. William Croft of London, heir of Henry Croft of Alisham 2. William Symonds of Norwich Messuage called Claptons in Groenington (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Deed, 21 April 18 Charles I (1642) 1. John Halman of Swaffham, Norfolk 2. Anthony Cannan of Swaffham 2 pieces of land in Swaffham (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Deed (Lease for 500 years), 22 May 21 Charles I (1645) 1. Edward Wilcham of Burlingham, Norfolk 2. John Pearse of Woodton, Norfolk 12 pieces of land in Burlingham (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Deed, 17 May 23 Charles I (1647) 1. Anthony Cannon of Swaffham, Norfolk 2. John Theodrick of Swaffham, Norfolk Land in Swaffham, Norfolk (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Deed (Lease for 20 years), 16 October 24 Charles I (1648) 1. George Lawe of Watton, Norfolk 2. Daniel Smith of Watton, Norfolk Land in Watton and/or Carbrooke (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 4 Deeds (Grant or Gift), 10 September 1651 1. Edward Garrett of Brancaster, husband 2. Robert Segon of Brancaster; Robert Reeder Lands in Brancaster Bond of William Godham of Brancaster 20 April 1675 30 January 1593 Edward Garrett, sen. 2 August 13 James I Lands in Brancaster (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Deed (Lease for 21 years), 1 March 1652 1. John Buckland of Westharptry, Somerset 2. John Landall of Hainford, Norfolk Land in Hainford (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Deed, 20 January 1656 1. William Lyncolne, the elder, of Hingham, Norfolk 2. Robert Downing of Hingham 2 houses in Hingham (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Deed, 20 October 12 Charles II (1660) 1. Robert Longe of Reymerston, Norfolk 2. Robert Ellis of Hingham, Norfolk Land in Hingham Manor (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Deed, 5 November 14 Charles II (1662) 1. William Marsham of Stratton Strawless 2. William Pecke of London 3 pieces of land in Haynford, Norfolk (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Deed (Power of Attorney), 4 April 1664 1. Aron Bartram of London, Yeoman authorizes 2. Roger Joyse, and others To represent him before the court of the Manor of Woodalling (Dallinghall) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Deed (Lease for 1,000 years), 24 June 1695 1. Joshua Foulser of Great Yarmouth 2. Nicholas Goddard of Shelfanger Land in Roydon (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Deed (Final Concord), William III (1698-99 ?) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Deed, 18 January 1699 1. Thomas Clipperton of Trymington 2. Robert Stapp of Hymingham Land in Trymington (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Deed, 24 June 1699 1. Bartholomew Stone of Minklewood 2. Thomas Claxton of Hackford (Hingham) 3. Peter Elwin of Cuttington Lands in Hackford (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Obligation Bond, 24 June 1699 1. Thomas Claxton of Harlford next Hingham 2. Peter Elwin of Tuttington 3. Bartholomew Stone Fullfillment of Indenture tripartite (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Deed (Mortgage-Lease for 1,000 years), 26 May 1699 1. John Faulke of Bunwell, Weaver; Thomas Faulke of Norwich, weaver 2. Robert Bendish of Norwich Land in Bunwell, Carleton Roads, and Wymondham (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Deed (Marriage Settlement), 1 September 1699 1. John Fowler of Southacre, yeoman 2. John Bagge of King's Lynn; Charles Bagge of Cockley Cley Lands in Stoke and Wretton (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Deed (Obligatory Bond), 23 November 1702 1. Thomas Whitby 2. Samuel Luidoe Concerning indenture of bargain and feofment (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Deed (Obligatory Bond), 2 October 1703 1. John Money, worstedweaver of Norwich; Jauniry Money, wife of William 2. William Money, bricklayer of London 3. Richard Sprat, baker of Norwich Concerning an indenture of Release (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Deed (Lease for 15 years), 24 November 1705 1. Henry Scarlett of Norton, yeoman 2. William Nelson of Dunham Land in Little Dunham (free and copyhold lands) (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Deed (Mortgage), 19 July 1707 1. William Newman of Baconesthorpe; Charles Hatton of London 2. Joseph Fox of Shadbrooke, Suffolk Lands in Shadbrooke Hoxon and Weybread in counties of Norfolk and Suffolk (Elizabeth Webb lent Newman and Hatton 360 for the use of Joseph Fox) (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Deed (Obligation - obligatory bond), 18 November 1707 1. Thomas Wade of Wearham 2. John Wright Concerning indenture of Bargain and Sale (Box 3, Folder 15)
- 3 deeds, Bargain and Sale 30 October 1708 1. Edmund Wright of Deeping 2. John Burkin of North Burlingham Lands in Tarrgate in Forncett St. Peter Copyhold Surrender 30 October 1708 1. Edmund Wright of North Burlingham 2. John Barking of North Burlingham Manor of Forncett Clarers Obligatory Bond 30 October 1708 1. Edmund Wright of Deepham 2. John Burkingham of North Burlingham Fullfill of Indenture of Release bearing same date (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Deed (Release), 2 September 1710 1. Ash Windham of Felbrigg 2. Horatio Townshend; Thomas Windham; and Joseph Windham (brothers of Ash) Lands in Gresham, Norfolk (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Deed (Articles of Agreement), 5 September 1717 1. Stephen Bond of Amringhallin 2. Peter May of Woodrising Land in ? (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Deed (Articles of Agreement, Bond), 18 May 1721 1. Thomas Allen of King's Lynn 2. Richard Berney of Norwich Involves South Sea Co. (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Deed, 10 June 30 Charles II (1678) 1. Mary Davy 2. Robert Freeman of Little Fransham Seven acres in Little Fransham (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Deed (Lease for 1 year), 5 March 1683 1. Jostina Greene of Kingston upon Hull 2. Woolestone Greene of King's Lynn Land in Lynn (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Deed, 18 April 1684 1. William Corie of Catton, Norfolk; William Chetleburgh of Hempnall 2. Richard Gay of Norwich (hosier) Lands in Woodton, Hempnall, Saxlingham, and Shottisham, Norfolk (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Deed (Lease for 99 years), 12 May 1684 1. Robt. Chettleburgh of Hempnall 2. Margrett Chettleburgh (grandchild of above) Lands in Hempnall (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Deed (Lease for 1 year), 29 June 36 Charles II (1684) 1. Christopher Grey of Little Barningham; Edward Grey of Holt 2. Lawrence Goodwin of Norwich 1 acre freehold in Colby (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Obligatory Bond, 10 October 36 Charles II (1684) 1. Robert Styleman 2. Nicholas Styleman Performances of indentures of Bargain and Sale (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Deed (Articles of Agreement), 16 April 1685 1. Robert Horner of Roydon 2. Hohn Greene of East Deereham Lands in Roydon, Norfolk (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Deed (Lease for 1,000 years) Cancelled, 25 October 1 James II (1685) 1. Charles Nedham of Westhorpe, Norfolk; Charles Shane of Lincoln's Inn; William Sedley of Morley Hall, Norfolk 2. Hugh Pratt of Old Buckenham, Norfolk 3. Henry Pratt of Old Buckenham, Norfolk; John Kendall of Norwich (trustees for Alice and Mary Pratt) Lands in Old Buckenham (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Deed (Release), 26 March 1690 1. George Smith of Topcroft, doctor 2. John Lane of Topcroft, yeoman Land in Topcroft (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 2 deeds, Mortgage 18 October 1690 1. Thomas Bransby of Great Forlingland 2. Edward Wigg of Shottesham St. Hilary Land in Porlingland (Manor of Framingham Earle) Copyhold 18 October 1690 1. Thomas Bransby 2. Edward Wigg Land in Manor of Framingham Earle (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Deed (Marriage Settlement), 6 April 1693 1. Mary Ward of Great Yarmouth; Benjamin Ward (son) 2. Thomas Atkins, merchant of Great Yarmouth 3. Sarah Atkins (daughter of Thomas) Lands in Great Yarmouth (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Deed, 26 July 1693 1. Francis Gooch of Slowley, sen.; Francis Gooch, jr. 2. Anthony Durrant of Hilborow Land in Hilborow (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Deed (Lease for 1 year), 11 October 1693 1. Thomas Harcoik of Woodton (Wootton); John Greene of Norwich 2. Roger Howman of Norwich, doctor Land in Woodton (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Deed (Lease for 80 years), 25 March 14 Charles II (1662) 1. Peter Cushinge of Norwich; Stephen Bullock of Lesingham; Robert Ward of Walcott 2. Robert Lambert of East Ruston, Norfolk; Robert Harmer of Great Yarmouth; John Harmer of Great Yarmouth Manor of Cardeston Netherhall in East Ruston (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Deed (Quit Claim), 20 August 1664 1. Alice Bartram (widow of Aron Bartram) 2. Edward Messinger Land in manor of Woodallinge (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Deed, 16 January 1665 1. Thomas Pincher of Great Fransham, Norfolk 2. Mathew Flegge of Great Fransham, Norfolk Land in Great Fransham (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Deed, 26 June 17 Charles II (1665) 1. Thomas Goulder of Trunche, Norfolk 2. Thomas Clipton of Trymingham Land in Trymingham (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Deed (Final Concord), 18 Charles II (1666-67) Lands in Woodton (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Deed, 8 June 1667 1. Christopher Cocke of Forncett, Norfolk 2. Charles George Cocke of Forncett, Norfolk Manor of Jermyes, alias Charston Jermyes Also land in Hapton, Moulton, and Stratton (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Deed, 16 March 1670 1. Thomas Lone of Mitford, Suffolk 2. John Billingsley of Norwich Land in Lingwood (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Deed (Marriage Settlement), 1 April 1670 1. John Theodricke of Swaffham 2. Thomas Theodricke; Mary Preist 3. Edmund Mott of Colket next Osborough; James Theodericke Lands in Swaffham (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Deed, 4 May 24 Charles II (1672) 1. Thomas Tricker of Ditclingham, Norfolk 2. Edward Mingay of Norton Subcrosse Lands in Bungay Burghe (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Deed, 1 January 26 Charles II (1674) 1. Richard Gogyll of Gymingham 2. Thomas Clipperton of Trymingham Land in Trymingham (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Deed (Articles of Agreement), 16 May 1674 1. William Doyly of Shottisham 2. Samuell Kerdon of Norwich; Marke Cockey, merchant of Norwich; Thomas Ball, leatherseller of London Lands in Shottisham (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Deed (Final Agreement - Recovery), 12 February 32 Charles II (1680) 1. Mathoes Chapman and Clement Smyth 2. Phillip Gaudy and Robert Hunte 40 acres in South Burlingham (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Deed (Lease for 9 years), 15 May 32 Charles (1680) 1. William Pecke of Hayneford, Norfolk 2. William Harrod of Hayneford, Norfolk Land in Hayneford (57 acres) (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Deed, 29 September 34 Charles II (1682) 1. Richard Huntington of Great Yarmouth 2. Henry Austine of Norwich Lands and buildings in Norwich (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Deed (Surrender and Admission), Extract of Court Roll 26 October 1646 1. Dorthea Skarnedale 2. John Holly, jr. Land in Manor of Holme, inc. Mare, qd Holkhams and Derrys (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Deed (Surrender and Admission), Extract of Court Roll 21 October 1652 1. Nicholas Blackborn of Holme next the Sea 2. John Holley the Younger 5 rods at Holme next the Sea; sometimes Holkhams and Berrys (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Deed (Surrender and Admission), 4 October 1653 1. Robert Slapp 2. Agnes Slapp Manor of Trymingham Lancaster (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Deed (Surrender and Admission), 5 July 16 Charles (1664) 1. John Streeke of Gymingham Lancaster 2. Dorothea Brandon Land in Manor of Gymingham Lancaster (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Deed (Copyhold), 23 April 18 Charles II (1665) Manor of Gymingham Lancaster exe Southrepps (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Deed, 20 December 1723 1. John Cusande of King's Lynn 2. Lawrence Turner of King's Lynn Land in King's Lynn (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Deed (Obligation), 30 March 1732 1. John Cusande of King's Lynn 2. William Lingay (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Deed (Obligation), 18 May 1734 1. Thomas Luelling of Hilburgh 2. Elizabeth Stallon of Ely, Isle of Ely Payment on Indenture of Release (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Deed, 18 November 1751 1. Richard Thorpe of Bylaugh; Elizabeth Thorpe of East Ruston 2. James Olnys of Witton Land in East Ruston (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Deed (Lease for 14 years), 29 December 1752 1. James Burkin of North Burlingham 2. Richard Read of Lingwood Land in South Burlingham (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Deed (Assignment of Mortgage; Securities in Trust), 27 September 1754 1. Thomas Morse of Norwich 2. Benjamin Nuthall K. Lynn 3. William Dye, merchant of Norwich 4. John Nuthall of Norwich Land in Norwich (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Deed, 7 February 1755 1. Stephen Gardnier of Norwich; Edmund Hooke of Norwich; Jermy Harcourt of Norwich 2. Henry Vale of Norwich, chapman 3. Benjamin Nuthall of King's Lynn; William Dye, merchant of Norwich Land in Norwich (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Final Concord, 12 George III (1771-72) 1. Thomas Beckett 2. John Hill Land in Bedingham, Woodton, Norton (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Final Concord, 13 George III (1772-73) 1. James Brown 2. John Game 3. Christophe West Lands in Nortwalsham and Thornage (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Deed (Lease for 7 years), 25 January 1802 1. John Astley of Thornage 2. Charles Beart of Horleston Lands in Horleston (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Deed (Surrender and Admission), 3 June 22 Charles II (1669) 1. John Lancaster of Heverton 2. Henry Nogus Lands in Hoverton St. Johns (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Deed (Surrender and Admission), 17 March 23 Charles II (1670) 1. John Bondson 2. Thomas Bond Lands in Manor of Thurgarton cum Basingham (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Deed (Extract of Court Roll), 18 March 24 Charles II (1671) Lands in Hackford Manor (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Deed (Surrender and Admission), 2 May 19 Charles II (1677) 1. Thomas Thompson 2. Thomas Clippton Land in Gymingham Lancaster (Tryningham vel Gymingham) (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Deed (Copyhold), 19 May 32 Charles II (1680) 1. 2. John Lowe Land in Hempnall Manor (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Deed (Copyhold), 5 October 33 Charles II (1681) 1. Antonius Rolfe 2. Anna Elwin ? Lands in Manor of Heydon cum membris (Box 6, Folder 2)
- 3 documents, Deed (Copyhold) 22 October 1684 1. Dorcae Springe 2. William Springe Lands in Manor of Brandon or Brandon's Ferry, Suffolk Receipt for payment of Copyhold fine for land bequeathed by William Springe Receipt for payment of Copyhold fine by Springe (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Deed (Copyhold), 15 October 3 James II (1687). 1. William and Anna Howard 2. Thome Clippton 3 rods of land in Trymingham in the Manor of Gymingham Lancaster (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Deed (Copyhold), 6 March 4 James II (1688) 1. Robert Atwood 2. Robert Atwood (son of above) 11 pieces (20 acres) in Manor of Ludham (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Deed (Copyhold), 4 February 13 William III (1701) 1. Thomas Slapp 2. Robert Slapp Gymingham Lancaster (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Deed (Copyhold), 23 April 13 William III (1701) 1. Richard Dix 2. Edi Dix Land in Southrepps (Manor of Gymingham Lancaster) (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Deed (Copyhold), 3 November 1709 Manor of Hempnall (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Deed (Copyhold), 2 November 1 George I (1714) Manor of Harleston (Thomas, Duke of Norfolk) (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Deed (Copyhold), 2 November 1714 1. Elizabeth Fuller 2. Jacobi King Manor of Herleston (Thomas, Duke of Norfolk) (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Deed (Copyhold), 19 November 6 George (1719) Manor of Ditchingham (Duke of Norfolk) (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Deed (Copyhold), 1 June 1721 1. Richard Doggett (father) 2. Richard Doggett (son) Manor of Harleston (Thomas, Duke of Norfolk) (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Deed (Copyhold), 7 November 1723 1. Willus Greygoose; Nathaniel Greygoose 2. Elizabeth and Thomas Greygoose 3. Jsaaco Chambers Manor of Harleston (Duke of Norfolk) (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Deed (Copyhold), 20 May 1 George II (1728) 1. Arthur Bush 2. John Bush Manor of Shelfhangerhall vice (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Deed (Copyhold), 29 and 30 October 1728 1. Frances Knight 2. Maria Cooper Land in Manor of Wymonham Cromwells (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Deed (Copyhold - surrender), 30 October 1731 1. Thomas Marsters 2. Thomas Marsters, jr. Manor of Shipdham (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Deed - (Copyhold), 18 July 7 George I (1733) 1. Phillip Girling of Bungay, Suffolk 2. Joseph King of Great Yarmouth One Salt Shop, Manor of Harleston (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Will, 24 May 1505 (Probated 10 March 10 Elizabeth (1568) Richard Bookinge of Longham, Norfolk (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Will, 13 November 1611 Randolph Smyth of Reedham, clerk Lands in Southwoode Lympenhawe, Cantley, Reedham, Frathorpp, and Moulton (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Will, 7 April 1647 Thomas Freeman of Wendling, yeoman Lands in Necton and Wendling (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Will, 30 July 1654 Andrew Wasiny of Carbrooke, yeoman (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Will, 24 September 1666 John Forman of Cullington, carpenter (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Will, 3 October 1674 Theodorus Hoste of St. Andrews Holborne, Middlesex Lands in Middlesex (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Deed (Copyhold), 18 July 7 George II (1733) 1. Robert Snell 2. Elizabeth Snell Manor of Harleston (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Deed (Copyhold), 6 June 10 George II (1737) 1. Margaret Beever 2. Thomas Beever Land in Manor of Brampton (Box 6, Folder 25)